welcome everybody I'm just going to give
欢迎我要给的所有人
you a brief presentations it will take
您将进行简短的演示
about 45 minutes and show you around the
大约45分钟，然后向您展示
new spring boot project for those that
那些新的春季启动项目
don't know you my name is Phil Webb
不知道你我叫菲尔·韦伯
I'm co-lead on spinning boots and also a
我是纺靴的共同负责人，也是
committer on the course spring framework
课程春季框架的提交者
so spring boot is a new project by
所以Spring Boot是一个新项目
spring and it's a project that we're
春天，这是我们的一个项目
introducing with the aim of getting
以获取为目的进行介绍
started with spring as quickly as
从春天开始
possible the idea is to take common
这个想法可能是普遍的
non-functional requirements that you
您的非功能性要求
need for a real application and make
需要一个真正的应用程序，使
them as easy as possible to use we're
他们尽可能容易使用我们
also trying to get away from as much as
还试图摆脱尽可能多的
possible any configuration that you'd
可能有您想要的任何配置
need to duplicate the idea with spring
需要与春天复制想法
boots as well is that we're going to try
靴子也是，我们要尝试
and focus the attention of a number of
并集中一些注意力
different spring projects so rather than
不同的春季项目，而不是
just being sprinkle or spring data we
只是被洒或弹簧数据，我们
prevent we present a unified way of
防止我们提出一种统一的方法
accessing the entire spring portfolio
访问整个春季投资组合
it's also an opportunity for a spring to
这也是春天的机会
actually be opinionated about the types
实际上对类型有意见
of technologies that you can use rather
您可以使用的技术
than go into too much detail with the
而不是将太多细节
slides I want to jump straight into some
我想直接跳入一些幻灯片
code and show you how it looks so I'm
代码并向您展示外观，所以我
going to start by demoing a greevey
首先要演示一个greevey
application and if you're a Java
应用程序，如果您是Java
developer don't worry we're going to
开发人员不用担心我们会
come on to Java a little bit but the
来一点点Java但
groovy story is a nice way to get
时髦的故事是一个很好的方法
started so I'm just going to go an empty
开始，所以我只是要空一个
directory here and I'm just going to
目录在这里，我只是去
start by editing an example phone so
首先编辑示例电话，以便
this example is just a typical hello
这个例子只是一个典型的问候
world and I'm going to use the spring
世界，我要用春天
wrist controller annotation and I'm
手腕控制器注释，我
going to annotate a class
要注释一堂课
so for those who haven't seen it before
所以对于那些以前没看过的人
rest controller is in the annotation
休息控制器在注释中
that's part of spring 4 and it's
那是春天4的一部分，
basically just a combination of act
基本上只是行为的组合
controller and at response body it just
控制器和响应主体
saves a you typing out response body on
保存您键入响应的正文
each of your methods it's a way of
您的每种方法都是一种
returning the result of a method
返回方法的结果
directly to the screen so I'm going to
直接转到屏幕上，所以我要
add a request wrapping for the route URL
为路由网址添加请求包装
and then just return a simple message
然后只返回一个简单的消息
okay so I just need to save this file
好的，所以我只需要保存此文件
there we go so if I want to run this
我们去了，所以如果我想运行这个
application spring boot ships with a
应用程序Spring Boot附带了一个
small command-line tool it's about five
小型命令行工具大约是五个
Meg and you can download it either as a
Meg，您可以将其下载为
zip file or if you're using a Mac you
zip文件，或者如果您使用的是Mac，
can use the brew install to get the
可以使用brew安装来获取
thing on your am system it's basically
你的系统上的东西基本上是
just a groovy compiler so if I want to
只是一个普通的编译器，所以如果我想
run this application I can just use
运行这个我可以使用的应用程序
spring run and then type in the name of
春季运行，然后输入名称
the file so then you can see the
该文件，这样您就可以看到
application starts we get a running
应用程序启动，我们开始运行
spring boot application and if I hit web
春季启动应用程序，如果我上网
browser I should be able to look at that
浏览器，我应该能够看到
local address and see the response hello
本地地址并查看回复你好
world email notice that added the - -
世界电子邮件通知中添加了--
watch option and this allows me to
观看选项，这使我能够
change the file and have it recompile as
更改文件并重新编译为
I do so I can I can simply save this
我这样做可以保存此内容
file again and then the console will
再次归档，然后控制台将
recognize it refresh and get the
识别它刷新并获取
immediate feedback so if we just recap
立即反馈，所以如果我们回顾一下
what happened there because it looks
那里发生了什么，因为看起来
kind of magical but it's I can assure
有点神奇，但是我可以保证
you it's not we started with a really
你不是我们从一个真正的开始
simple example here just a rest
简单的例子在这里休息
controller we're doing that request
控制器，我们正在执行该请求
mapping and returning the response but
映射并返回响应，但是
but spring boot is actually doing a
但是弹簧靴实际上正在做一个
number of things behind the scenes for
幕后的事物数量
us so let's step through these and see
我们，让我们逐步了解这些
what they are one by one the first thing
他们一一被第一
that happens is spring boot adds a
发生的是弹簧靴增加了一个
import statements for the things that
导入声明的东西
you're likely to need so I didn't have
您可能需要，所以我没有
to add the import org dot Spring
添加导入组织点Spring
Framework web bind annotation just
框架Web绑定注释
because I want to use the rest
因为我想用剩下的
controller because it happens
控制器，因为它发生了
automatically and we had a number of
自动，我们有一些
imports for the things that you're
进口你所要的东西
likely to want to use the next thing
可能想使用下一件事
that happens is we take a look at your
发生的情况是我们看一下您的
application
应用
nation and we make a guess about the
国家，我们对
type of things that you're going to need
您将需要的东西类型
and so for example because this is a
例如，因为这是一个
rest controller application we're going
剩下的控制器应用程序，我们要去
to assume that you want to run it within
假设您要在其中运行
a website so we have a web starter if
一个网站，所以我们有一个网络启动器，如果
you haven't seen it before this grab
你在抓之前还没看过
annotation is something that groovy
注释是很时髦的
provides and it's basically the
提供，基本上是
equivalent of doing a maven build valve
相当于做一个Maven建造阀
directly in your in your class so it
直接在您的班级中
just says I need to get these
只是说我需要得到这些
dependencies to run the application the
运行应用程序的依赖项
next thing that happens is we add this
接下来发生的事情是我们添加了这个
enabled water configuration annotation
启用水配置注释
and this is part of spring boot that
这是 spring boot 的一部分
allows it to attempt to guess the
允许其尝试猜测
configuration that you're likely to need
您可能需要的配置
so again because we're doing a rest
再说一次，因为我们正在休息
controller we're going to set up spring
控制器，我们将要设置弹簧
MVC for you automatically with the dis
MVC自动为您提供Dis
annotation and I'll cover this in a bit
注释，我会稍作介绍
more detail when we get to the job and
我们上班时会有更多细节，
the last thing that happens is we have
最后发生的事情是我们有
to add a main method so this allows us
添加一个主要方法，这样我们可以
to actually launch the application and
实际启动该应用程序并
this simply delegates off to another
这只是委托给另一个
spring boot class called spring
弹簧靴类称为弹簧
application and again I'll cover that in
应用程序，我将再次介绍
more detail I should notice now you
现在我应该注意到更多细节
should note as well that this is not
还应该注意，这不是
changing your source code this is
更改您的源代码是
actually changing the compiled bytecode
实际更改已编译的字节码
so your source remains unchanged as you
因此您的来源将保持不变
as you work on it so if you've seen the
当您进行这项工作时，如果您已经看过
groov example now and you put in all the
groov示例，现在您将所有
things that happen for you you can see
发生在你身上的事情你可以看到
that it's starting to look a lot more
它开始看起来更多了
like a classic java application and we
就像经典的Java应用程序一样，我们
do actually provide first-class Java
确实提供一流的Java
support and spring boots so what I want
支撑和弹簧靴，所以我想要什么
to do now is take the same application
现在要做的是使用相同的应用程序
that we just wrote in groovy and write
我们只是用groovy写的
it within Java
它在Java中
inside the new IDE so I've got an empty
在新的IDE中，所以我有一个空白
project set up here and I'm using maven
项目在这里设置，我正在使用Maven
for this project but you could just as
这个项目，但你可以
easily use Gradle if that's your
如果这是您的话，请轻松使用Gradle
preference then a couple of special
偏好，然后几个特殊
things that I've set up the first is
我首先设置的是
that I've got some repository
我有一些仓库
definitions because I'm pulling in
定义，因为我要加入
snapshot and milestone releases because
快照和里程碑版本的发布是因为
we haven't actually released a full GA
我们实际上还没有发布完整的GA
yet a spring boot
spring boot
the other thing that I've got that's
我得到的另一件事是
important is I'm inheriting from this
重要的是我要从中继承
parent pom and this is a nice little
父母pom，这是一个很好的小
convenience that we provide with spring
我们为春天提供的便利
boot you don't have to use it but if you
引导您不必使用它，但是如果您
do it it just makes your maven file a
这样做只会使您的Maven文件
little bit easier to them to write and
他们写起来容易一点，
you can see that by default we provide a
您可以看到，默认情况下，我们提供了
number of test dependencies that you're
您正在测试的依赖项数
likely to use so J unit and hamcrest so
可能会使用J单位和hamcrest这样
I want to actually write the the same
我想写一样的东西
best controller in Java the first thing
Java最佳控制器的第一件事
that I really need to do is get the
我真正需要做的是
dependency that was added automatically
自动添加的依赖项
by the groovy code so with maven I can
通过常规代码，因此使用Maven我可以
just search for a dependency spring blue
只是寻找一个依赖春天蓝色
provides a number of starter poms and
提供了一些入门的poms和
starter ponds are just a way of grouping
初学者池塘只是分组的一种方式
common dependencies that you're likely
您可能的常见依赖关系
to need over and over again so in this
需要一遍又一遍，所以在这个
case because I'm writing a web
案例，因为我正在写网
application I'm going to use the spring
我要用弹簧的应用程序
starter web pom you notice that all of
入门网络pom，您会注意到所有
the starters begin in the same way so
起动器以相同的方式开始，因此
they're easy to search for if you want
他们很容易搜索，如果你想
to try and discover the the type of
尝试发现
things that we support so I save this
我们支持的事情，所以我保存下来
file you'll now see that we get a bunch
文件，您现在会看到我们得到了一堆
of extra dependencies that have been
已经有额外的依赖
pulled in through this starter pond so
通过这个初学者池塘拉
we have spring MVC obviously because
我们有春季MVC显然是因为
we're writing a rest controller we have
我们正在编写一个休息控制器
spring boot itself and we have tomcat
弹簧靴本身，我们有雄猫
embedded which is going to provide the
嵌入式将提供
actual server context so let's get on
实际的服务器上下文，让我们继续
and actually write that class that we
并实际写那个我们
need so the first thing I want to do is
需要，所以我要做的第一件事是
annotate it with rest controller as
用rest控制器注释它为
before and then I need to add that
之前然后我需要添加
enable auto configuration annotation
启用自动配置注释
because that doesn't happen
因为那不会发生
automatically in the Java world and this
自动在Java世界中
is just opting in to the to the auto
只是选择加入汽车
configuration functionality that we
我们的配置功能
provide and I want to write my actual
提供，我想写我的实际
functionality
功能性
I need to use request mapping not to not
我需要使用请求映射不要
wrest control earlier and the last thing
抢先控制，最后一件事
that I need to do is add the main method
我需要做的是添加main方法
again something that happens
再次发生的事情
automatically in the groovy world which
在groovy世界中自动
you have to do yourself here and I'm
你必须在这里自己做，我是
just going to delegate off to the spring
只是去代表春天
application class and call the static
应用程序类并调用静态
convenience run method and the source of
便捷运行方法及来源
my application is this class itself and
我的应用程序是此类本身，
then let's just pass through the
然后让我们通过
arguments from the command line as they
来自命令行的参数
are so that should be all I need to get
所以应该就是我所需要的
this application running and if I want
该应用程序正在运行，如果我想
to actually start it I can just run from
真正开始，我可以从
within a IDE and hopefully this
在IDE中，希望这
application starts up if you get the
如果您得到应用程序启动
same kind of output as you do on the
与您在
groovy code and then if i refresh my
常规代码，然后如果我刷新我的
screen you see that we're now running
屏幕上您看到我们正在运行
within the IDE so let's just recap what
在IDE中，所以让我们回顾一下
happened there we have this application
发生在那里我们有这个应用程序
class again we have to remember to add
再次上课，我们要记得添加
the enable auto configuration and the
启用自动配置和
main method so that we can start it but
主要方法，以便我们可以启动它，但是
otherwise it's pretty simple and we have
否则很简单，我们有
the the request mapping that actually
实际的请求映射
does the work so just to recap the
做这项工作是为了总结
starter problems are a nice way to give
入门者问题是解决问题的一种好方法
you these kind of dependencies things
你这些依赖的东西
that we recommend all work together we
我们建议大家一起努力
have this optional parent pom that you
有这个可选的父pom
can use which helps cut down your may
可以使用它有助于减少您的可能
even config and we provide starters for
甚至配置，我们为
a number of projects including web batch
许多项目，包括网络批处理
integration and spring data I should
我应该整合和弹簧数据
mention as well these are not just
还提这些不只是
spring dependencies that we provide in
我们提供的spring依赖
the starters they're actually
他们实际上是首发
third-party dependencies as well so for
第三方依赖也是如此
instance if you take a data starter you
实例，如果您使用数据入门
will get spring data but also hibernate
将获得 spring data ，但也会休眠
and jsr 303 annotations to enable you to
和jsr 303批注，使您能够
do validation
做验证
the next part that we had to do was
接下来我们要做的是
create the the run method from the main
从主创建运行方法
and call the spring application class
并调用spring应用程序类
and this in most of the time you can
在大多数时候，您可以
just call spring application don't run
只是调用spring应用程序不运行
occasionally you may want to do some
有时您可能想做一些
customization of your application before
定制您的应用之前
it starts so if you want to you can also
它开始，所以如果您愿意，也可以
use an instance of it so this this code
使用它的一个实例，所以这段代码
at the top shows how I can create a
顶部显示了如何创建一个
spring application and then customize it
春天的应用程序，然后对其进行自定义
in this case I'm just turning off the
在这种情况下，我只是关闭
little spring leaf banner that gets
得到的小春叶横幅
displayed and then I run it as I would
显示，然后按我的方式运行
would before the spring application
在春季申请之前
class itself is pretty straightforward
类本身非常简单
it's only got one job and that's to give
它只有一份工作，那就是给
you a spring application context if
您是Spring应用程序上下文，如果
you're using a web application then you
您正在使用网络应用程序，然后
get an embedded web application context
获取嵌入式Web应用程序上下文
which is a new type provided by spring
这是spring提供的一种新型
boots and this is just a quick way of
靴子，这只是一种快速的方法
getting up and running with an embedded
嵌入式运行并运行
servlet container and out of the box we
servlet容器，开箱即用
support Tomcat and we also support jetty
支持Tomcat，我们也支持码头
if you want to add additional servers
如果要添加其他服务器
the interface is fairly simple so it
界面非常简单，所以它
should be possible to if you're not
如果你不应该应该
writing a web application then the
编写一个Web应用程序，然后
application context is just a standard
应用程序上下文只是一个标准
annotation driven application context
注释驱动的应用程序上下文
the next thing that we needed to do was
接下来我们要做的是
enable this auto configuration
启用此自动配置
annotation and this is this is the way
注释，这就是这种方式
to opt into spring boots Auto
选择加入 spring boot
configuration functionality the way this
配置功能的方式
works is it takes a look at your class
有用吗，它需要看你的课
path and tries to make an educated guess
路径并尝试做出有根据的猜测
about what configuration you would
关于您将要配置什么
normally want to create so for example
通常要创建这样，例如
in this in this case because it we have
在这种情况下，因为它有
Tomcat on the class path then we're
Tomcat在类路径上，然后
going to try and Auto configure you a
将尝试并自动配置您一个
tomcat server the way these
这些tomcat服务器的方式
configurations work actually they're
配置工作实际上他们
standard at configuration spring classes
配置弹簧等级的标准
with a couple of additional annotations
带有几个附加注释
spring 4 is going to introduce a new
春季4将引入一个新的
conditional annotation we
条件注释
to allow you to conditionally choose
让你有条件地选择
whether beans that are created or not
是否创建了bean
it's a bit like app profile but um for
这有点像应用程序配置文件，但对于
programmatically determining whether it
以编程方式确定是否
being is created most of the auto
被创造了大部分的自动
configuration that we provide is
我们提供的配置是
conditional on class which means that
有条件的，这意味着
it'll work only if a particular classes
它只有在特定的班级才有效
on your class path and also conditional
在你上课的路上，也是有条件的
on missing being which means that if you
缺少存在，这意味着如果你
define your own beans to take care of
定义自己的豆子来照顾
that particular part of the
该特定部分
functionality then spring Google back
功能，然后弹回Google
away and we've got a demo of that I'll
走了，我们有一个演示，我将
show you a bit later so the next thing I
稍后再告诉你，接下来我
want to show you is how you can take
想告诉你如何去做
this application which is running within
该应用程序正在其中运行
your IDE and package it up so that you
您的IDE并将其打包，以便您
can actually ship it and deploy it
可以实际运送并部署它
somewhere spring boot provides a nice
spring boot 提供了一个不错的地方
Java plugin for maven and also a plug-in
适用于Maven的Java插件，也是一个插件
for Gradle that you can use so I'm just
您可以使用的Gradle，所以我只是
going to insert the spring boot million
要插入弹簧靴子万
plugin
插入
if I save that then jump to the command
如果我保存了，那么跳转到命令
line and build project manually we can
排队并手动构建项目，我们可以
see look at the output so here's my
看看输出，这是我的
project you can see the the basic
您可以看到基本的项目
classes that we've got I'm just going to
我要去的课程
do maven clean install to build it so if
做maven clean install来构建它，如果
we take a look in the target directory
我们来看看目标目录
now you can see that we have a couple of
现在您可以看到我们有几个
jar files we have an original jar file
jar文件，我们有一个原始的jar文件
which is the version that Nathan would
那是内森会的版本
normally create and that's weighing in
通常创建并且权衡
at about 3k which kind of figures
大约3k什么样的数字
because we haven't written much of our
因为我们还没有写很多
own code but we also have this new jar
自己的代码，但我们也有这个新的jar
file that the maven plug-in is created
创建Maven插件的文件
for us and that's about nine Meg and
对我们来说大约是九兆
this is a special type of jar that you
这是一种特殊的罐子
can actually run I'll just show you the
可以实际运行，我只向您展示
contents of it
它的内容
so here you can see we have the kind of
所以在这里您可以看到我们有一种
standard things that maven will produce
Maven将产生的标准东西
a pom file
一个pom文件
there's the class that we wrote
有我们写的课
ourselves and then we have an additional
自己，然后我们还有一个
Lib folder which contains all the
Lib文件夹，其中包含所有
dependencies that we've got so here you
我们已经有了依赖性，所以在这里你
can see we have dependencies on spring
可以看到我们对spring有依赖性
boot and Tomcat and Jackson these are
引导和Tomcat和Jackson这些是
fairly easy to read and it's very
相当容易阅读，而且非常
similar to the wire file format that you
类似于您的有线文件格式
can only get in web in flip so if you're
只能以翻转方式进入网络，所以如果您
familiar with that it should be fairly
熟悉它应该相当
straightforward to understand there are
容易理解
also a couple of additional classes that
还有一些其他的课程
get written and these are just required
被写，这些只是必需的
so that we can support running natively
这样我们就可以支持本机运行
you don't need to worry about too much
您不必担心太多
so if I want to run that application I
因此，如果我想运行该应用程序，
can now just type Java - gr and then the
现在可以只键入Java-gr，然后
name of the jar file and this will now
jar文件的名称，现在
start up and I can hit refresh and see
启动，我可以点击刷新以查看
that it's running so as I said we've got
它正在运行，所以正如我所说的，
a navin plugin and a Gradle plugin so
一个navin插件和一个Gradle插件
you're free to use either of those build
您可以自由使用其中任何一个
systems and we also provide a
系统，我们还提供了
general-purpose Java library so if you
通用Java库，如果您
need something a bit more exotic you can
需要一些更奇特的东西
hook into that these are jar files fat
知道这些是jar文件胖
jar files I think are really useful
我认为jar文件真的很有用
because they're very easy to understand
因为它们很容易理解
you don't need to unpack them you don't
您不需要拆开它们的包装
need to ship any start scripts and as
需要运送任何启动脚本，并作为
you can see a typical West rest app is
您可以看到一个典型的West rest应用是
is coming in at around 10 megabytes
即将达到10兆字节
which is nice and small they're also
很好，也很小，他们也是
really friendly to use with Cloud
与Cloud一起使用时非常友好
Foundry so if you deploy your
铸造，所以如果您部署您的
applications to a cloud service then
然后将应用程序迁移到云服务
these archives can work really well so
这些档案可以很好地运作
the example application that I wrote was
我编写的示例应用程序是
a web application but you don't have to
Web应用程序，但您不必
use spring the to write web applications
使用spring编写Web应用程序
you can actually write any type of
你实际上可以写任何类型的
applications we provide a couple of
我们提供一些应用程序
little hook points that you can use the
小钩点，您可以使用
first is a command line runner which is
首先是命令行运行程序
a simple interface that basically
一个简单的界面，基本上
mirrors the main method that you would
反映您将要使用的主要方法
call so you can create a bean implement
调用，以便您可以创建一个bean实现
this interface and then handle any kind
此接口，然后处理任何类型
of code that you want to we also provide
您还希望提供的代码
a convenient way of getting command line
获取命令行的便捷方法
arguments actually into spring so
实际上争论进入春天
anything you specify with a dash dash on
您指定的任何带有破折号的
the command line will become available
命令行将变为可用
in the spring environment and you can
在春季环境中，您可以
then inject those values straight into
然后将这些值直接注入
your beans so we use this actually
您的豆子，所以我们实际使用它
internally with boot itself and you can
内部使用启动本身，您可以
configure many aspects of boot using
使用以下命令配置引导的许多方面
command line so for instance if you do -
命令行，例如，如果您这样做-
- server dot port you can change the
-服务器点端口可以更改
port number from the default of 8080 to
端口号从默认的8080到
something that you want we also give you
您想要的东西我们也给您
a way to work with configuration files
一种使用配置文件的方法
and properties files a spring bube we
和属性文件的弹簧箱我们
have a convention of looking for a file
约定寻找文件
called applications or properties and
称为应用程序或属性
you can put that file either on your
您可以将该文件放在您的
class path or next to your jar so I'll
课堂路径或您的jar旁边，我会
give you a quick demo of that so let's
给你一个快速的演示，让我们
change this control that we've got and
更改我们拥有的控件，
make it a bit more useful what I'm going
使我的工作变得更有用
to do is inject a value into this
要做的就是为此注入一个值
private field and a call name which I
专用字段和我的通话名称
will get from Springs environment and
将从Springs环境获得
then I'll change this hello world to be
然后我将这个世界变成
hello name so if I want to have that
你好名字，所以如果我想拥有那个
name configurable I can actually create
我实际上可以创建的可配置名称
a local properties file so let's just
一个本地属性文件，让我们
put one in the source main as also spoke
也把一个放在来源主语中
Asian
亚洲人
and I can just use name equals and then
我可以使用名字等于
stick my name in so if I run this
坚持我的名字，所以如果我运行这个
application again and then hit the web
再次申请，然后上网
browser with this time we're getting
这次的浏览器
hello Phil and if I jump back into the
你好，菲尔，如果我跳回
command line we could we could change
命令行我们可以改变
that file locally it's just rebuild the
该文件在本地只是重建
project again and then I can echo and
再次投影，然后我可以回显和
then it was Dave to a local property as
然后是戴夫（Dave）
well and then if I run this application
好，然后如果我运行此应用程序
again locally and refresh you'll see
再次在本地刷新，您将看到
that it's picking up that properties in
它正在拾取的属性
preference so we still have the the
偏好，因此我们仍然有
properties within the jar and that will
罐子里的属性，这将
still get applied it's just the outer
仍然得到应用，这只是外部
file will then take precedence so this
文件将具有优先权，因此
is a really nice way of offering a way
是提供方法的一种非常好的方法
to configure your applications you can
配置您的应用程序，您可以
have a fairly complete configuration
具有相当完整的配置
bundle with your app and allow people
与您的应用捆绑在一起，并允许其他人
just override the bits that they want to
只是覆盖他们想要的位
locally you can also use the command
在本地您也可以使用以下命令
line arguments so I can I can replace
行参数，以便我可以替换
this again with a command line argument
再次使用命令行参数
which will take precedent from the local
这将是当地的先例
file and refresh in this there's the
文件并在其中刷新
local option
本地选择
if you don't want to use properties
如果您不想使用属性
files you can use yeah Moe and yeah Moe
您可以使用yeah Moe和yeah Moe的文件
is really popular especially in the Ruby
真的很受欢迎，尤其是在Ruby中
world and it's a really nice format for
世界，这是一个非常不错的格式
configuration fast and if you want to
快速配置，如果您想
easily amyl you just have to include the
轻松戊基，您只需要包括
snake yam all library on your class path
山药蛇
and then you can replace application dot
然后您可以替换应用程序点
properties or use them in conjunction
属性或结合使用
with application channel and both of
与应用程序通道和
those files will result in in thoughts
这些文件将导致思想
separated values ending up on the
分隔的值最后出现在
environment so here you can see how
环境，所以在这里您可以看到
server dot port could be specified using
可以使用以下命令指定服务器点端口
Yammer we also provide a way within
Yammer我们还提供了一种
spring boot to bind properties to
Spring Boot将属性绑定到
classes directly and this can be very
直接上课，这可能非常
useful if you've got a more structured
如果您的结构更合理，则很有用
format and you want to make sure that it
格式，并且您要确保它
the properties file is correctly
属性文件正确
configured so here we have an example
配置，所以这里有一个例子
where we have a class called my
我们有一班叫我的
properties with a couple of member
有几个成员的属性
variables location and skip and we have
变量位置和跳过，我们有
an apt configuration properties
apt配置属性
annotation the tell spring boot this is
注释告诉弹簧靴子这是
a spring bean that should be bound with
应当与之结合的春豆
values from the properties so you can
属性中的值，以便您可以
look and see that application that
看看那个应用程序
properties below defines a couple of
以下属性定义了几个
string values classpath mine xml and
字符串值classpath我的xml和
skip is false and actually binds those
skip是错误的，实际上将那些绑定
two real strong types within the Java
Java中两个真正的强类型
world so in this case the spring
世界，所以在这种情况下，春天
resource abstraction and the boolean now
资源抽象和布尔值
we actually use this within spring boots
我们实际上在 spring boot 中使用它
itself so for instance if I show you
本身，例如，如果我告诉你
there's a class called server properties
有一个叫做服务器属性的类
and this is the properties that we use
这就是我们使用的属性
to define server settings so you can see
定义服务器设置，以便您可以看到
we have a prefix of server and then dot
我们有一个服务器前缀，然后点
port was the thing that we set early and
端口是我们提早设置的东西，
there's a number of other things that
还有很多其他事情
you can you consent
你可以同意
so if you don't want to use application
因此，如果您不想使用应用程序
dot properties as your name you can
点属性可以作为您的名字
change it you can specify a spring
改变它你可以指定一个弹簧
config dot name or spring conflict
配置点名称或弹簧冲突
location if you want to change is the
如果要更改的位置是
name or the location that that file is
该文件的名称或位置
picked up from and you can do this
从那里捡起，你可以做到这一点
either on the command line or you can
在命令行上，或者您可以
set it in the environment directly and
将其直接放置在环境中，
that will change the way that the file
这将改变文件的方式
is picked up so we strive to make most
被捡起，所以我们努力做到最大
things in Boo customizable so if you
Boo中的内容可自定义，因此，如果您
don't like any of the decisions that
不喜欢任何决定
we've made you should be able to change
我们让您应该能够改变
them with relative ease another nice
他们相对轻松另一个好
feature about the properties files is
有关属性文件的功能是
the fact that we can support profiles
我们可以支持个人资料的事实
with them very easily so if you use
与他们非常容易，所以如果您使用
Springs at profile annotation perhaps
出现在轮廓注释中
you have a different set of
你有不同的一套
configuration that you use for
您用于的配置
production versus development then you
生产与发展然后你
can have a different properties file
可以有一个不同的属性文件
that gets picked up automatically based
会自动根据
on that convention so here you can see
按照那个惯例，所以在这里你可以看到
that because we're enabling the
那是因为我们正在启用
development profile application -
开发配置文件应用程序-
development of properties will be loaded
开发的属性将被加载
with the animal it's even nicer because
与动物在一起，甚至更好，因为
you can have a nested document to define
你可以有一个嵌套的文档来定义
the particular profiles to actually set
实际设置的特定配置文件
the active profiles you can use the
您可以使用的活动配置文件
spring profiles active trigger so you
弹簧型材主动触发，因此您
can either do that on the command line
可以在命令行上做到这一点
or you could put it in the properties
或者您可以将其放在属性中
file in fact any way that you can get it
实际上以任何方式获取文件
into the environment will be respected
进入环境将受到尊重
by spring boot spring boot ships with
通过spring boot spring boot随带
support for three common logging
支持三种常见的日志记录
frameworks log back log4j and java.util
框架重新登录log4j和java.util
logging by default if you use the
如果您使用
starter ponds then you'll get logged
初学者池塘，然后您将被记录
back and we strive to make sure that the
返回，我们努力确保
output for the log looks sensible and
日志的输出看起来很明智，
also that the various different logging
还要指出各种不同的日志记录
implementations that the libraries use
库使用的实现
may have made use of will be piped
可能已经利用过
through and work correctly so you may
通过并正确工作，这样您就可以
have noticed that when I started the app
注意到当我启动应用程序时
on the command line I got nice single
在命令行上我得到了不错的单身
line output with colored highlighting
彩色突出显示的行输出
if you want to change any of the locking
如果您想更改任何锁定
configuration it's pretty
配置很漂亮
straightforward you can just create a
直接，您可以创建一个
log file properties depending on the
日志文件属性取决于
actual system that you were using and
您正在使用的实际系统
ship that with your application if you
随您的应用程序一起运送
want to take a look at how this actually
想看看这实际上如何
works there's a class called logging
工作有一个称为日志记录的类
application context initializer which is
应用程序上下文初始化器是
the route way that spring boots actually
弹簧实际启动的路线方式
starts out the logging what I want to do
开始记录我想做的事
now is really take you through a demo of
现在真的带您通过演示
how auto configuration works just to try
自动配置如何工作只是为了尝试
and clarify a few things so what I want
并澄清一些事情，我想要什么
to do is jump back into that code and
要做的就是跳回该代码，
what I'm going to do is change this
我要做的就是改变这个
class so that instead of printing out a
类，而不是打印出一个
name is going to print out information
名称将打印出信息
from a data source I'm just going to
从数据源中，我只是要
inject that data source so here I've got
注入数据源，所以我在这里
a new data source inject it in and then
一个新的数据源将其注入，然后
I'm going to change this output I had to
我将不得不更改此输出
just get some information from the
只是从中获取一些信息
connection in this case so I'm going to
在这种情况下连接，所以我要
return the database vendor from the
从数据库返回数据库供应商
metadata
元数据
so if I start this application again
所以如果我再次启动这个应用程序
what's going to happen now is we're
现在要发生的是
actually going to get an exception in
实际上会在
this case where we're game told that we
在这种情况下，我们被游戏告知
haven't actually got any data source
实际上没有任何数据源
defined and that makes sense because we
定义，这是有道理的，因为我们
dependencies on our hospice so spring
春天来了，对我们的临终关怀的依赖
boot can't really attempt to create
引导无法真正尝试创建
configuration for us so if I change my
我们的配置，所以如果我更改我的
pom file I can correct that I'm just
POM文件，我可以纠正我只是
going to have a couple of dependencies
将有几个依赖
I'm going to add spring JDBC and then
我将添加spring JDBC，然后
I'll add hsqldb as a as my database you
我将hsqldb添加为我的数据库
may notice that none of the version
可能会注意到没有版本
numbers are appearing in this pom file
数字显示在此pom文件中
and that's due to the parent having to
那是由于父母必须
find a bunch of for the defaults for me
为我找到一堆默认值
so if I restart this application again
因此，如果我再次重新启动此应用程序
this time it started and if i refresh I
这次开始了，如果我刷新我
get that information about the
获得有关的信息
particular database engine that we're
我们所使用的特定数据库引擎
using so if I go ahead and maybe swap
使用，如果我继续，也许交换
this out for something different we can
为了不同的东西，我们可以
see how the auto configuration will
看看自动配置如何
manage that for us I'll swap it for the
为我们管理，我将其交换为
h2 database
h2数据库
and there we go if I was to define my
如果我要定义我的，那我们就走了
own being definition locally for a data
自己在本地定义数据
source then spring boot would see that
来源，然后春季启动会看到
and not get involved at all so in this
完全不参与其中
case it's going to create in-memory
它将在内存中创建
databases but if I want to move to
数据库，但是如果我想移至
production and pointed at a real
生产，并指出一个真正的
database then then that's easy enough
数据库，那么这很容易
for me to do within my own configuration
由我自己配置
so currently for a water configuration
所以目前用于水配置
we offer a bunch of things and we're
我们提供了很多东西，我们
always looking for more so if you find
总是在寻找更多，所以如果你发现
something that's missing and something
缺少的东西
that you think we should support then
那你认为我们应该支持
please add github issue there's an
请添加github问题，有一个
interesting blog post recently about the
最近关于
steps that one of our team took to add
我们的团队之一采取的添加步骤
support so that's a good starting point
支持，这是一个很好的起点
if you want to read that out of the box
如果您想直接阅读
we currently give you support for
我们目前为您提供支持
embedded servlet containers so we offer
嵌入式servlet容器，因此我们提供
Tomcat and jetty we can auto why you add
Tomcat和码头我们可以自动为您添加内容
data source and JDBC templates we have
数据源和JDBC模板
JPA support and spring data JPA so this
JPA支持和Spring数据JPA这样
is a really nice way of working with JPA
是使用JPA的一种非常不错的方法
entities and I really recommend the
实体，我真的推荐
spring day to join a project if you
如果您有参加项目的春季
haven't used it already we can also give
还没用过，我们也可以给
you timely for web templating and we
您及时进行网络模板制作，我们
have support for the usual spring
对平常的春天有支持
projects batch etc we also have support
项目批处理等我们也有支持
for reactor which is a new pivotal
对于反应堆这是一个新的关键
project which is really helpful for
这个项目确实有帮助
doing super fast data ingestion and
进行超快速的数据提取
asynchronous processing that's a very
异步处理非常
interesting project that's getting a lot
有趣的项目越来越多
of attention at the last feature that I
我最后一个功能的关注点
want to cover is actuator and actuator
要覆盖的是执行器和执行器
is an additional dependency that you can
是您可以附加的依赖
add if you want to add production-ready
如果要添加生产就绪则添加
features so I'm going to jump back to
功能，因此我将跳回
the code and show you how that looks so
代码并向您展示它的外观
as with everything we have a starter for
就像我们拥有的入门产品一样
the actuator I just need to include
我只需要包括的执行器
and if I restart the application now we
如果我现在重新启动应用程序，我们
should see some additional end points
应该看到一些其他终点
have been mapped so here we have some
已经被映射，所以在这里我们有一些
additional info endpoints and endpoints
其他信息端点和端点
metrics and what have you so if I jump
指标，如果我跳了，你有什么想法
back to my web browser my application
回到我的网络浏览器我的应用程序
still runs as it always did but I now
仍然像往常一样运行，但我现在
have some additional information that I
还有一些其他信息，我
can get so for instance if I hit beans
可以得到，例如，如果我打豆子
then I can get a JSON response that
然后我可以得到一个JSON响应
shows me all the beans that are part of
告诉我所有的豆子
this application or I can do a thread
这个应用程序，或者我可以做一个线程
dump right should be putting slash dump
转储权应该放在斜线转储
and then I get the information for all
然后我得到所有的信息
the threads that are currently running
当前正在运行的线程
we also offer simple health checking so
我们还提供简单的健康检查，因此
if you have health you can write your
如果你健康，可以写你的
own implementation here that maybe
自己的实现，也许
checks a database or looks to see if
检查数据库或查看是否
some network connection works so it's
一些网络连接有效，因此
really useful for monitoring and we also
对于监控非常有用，我们还
provide useful trace and metric
提供有用的跟踪和指标
information so if I hit trace you can
信息，所以如果我点击跟踪，您可以
see the recent requests that I've had
查看我最近收到的请求
made the application information about
使有关的应用程序信息
the headers that came through the user
通过用户的标题
agent the response and if I hit metrics
代理响应，如果我达到指标
I get information about the various URLs
我得到有关各种URL的信息
that have been hit so in this case you
被击中，所以在这种情况下，您
let's look at Reuters the slash and the
让我们看看路透社的斜线和
status that Wister terms 200 and I hit
Wister决定我打200的状态
that once if I go over here and refresh
一次，如果我去这里刷新
this page a few times then you can see
此页面几次，您可以看到
that counter goes up and these are
那个计数器上升，这些是
fairly simple in-memory representations
相当简单的内存表示
at the moment that keep you know the
此刻让你知道
last so many bits of data
持续这么多数据
so those are actuator then adds these
所以这些是执行器，然后添加这些
production-ready features things that
生产就绪的功能
you're likely to need when you get to
当您到达时可能会需要
production it exposes them via spring
生产它通过春天暴露了他们
MVC endpoints and it provides
MVC端点，它提供
information like the metrics and health
指标和健康状况等信息
either locally you can you can access
您可以在本地访问
them using the same port so if you're
他们使用相同的端口，所以如果你是
deploying to a powered environment
部署到动力环境
that's very useful or if you're running
这非常有用，或者如果您正在跑步
in your own data center you can also
在您自己的数据中心中，您还可以
specify a different port for the
指定其他端口
actuator endpoints so with a simple
执行器端点，因此简单
configuration choice you can decide to
您可以决定的配置选择
not expose them on your main site if you
如果您不公开他们在您的主要站点
want to add secure to the endpoints so
想要向端点添加安全性，以便
some of this information you may not
其中一些信息您可能不会
want to expose then it's pretty
想揭露那很漂亮
straightforward all you need to do is
您只需要做的就是
add spring security so I'll just give
增加春季安全性，所以我就给
you a quick demo of that again we have a
您再次进行快速演示，我们有一个
starter for this
初学者
so spring starter security so I just
所以春季初学者安全，所以我只是
have to add that dependency and again
必须再次添加该依赖项
spring boot will see the new things on
春季靴将看到新的事物
the class path and configure it
类路径并配置它
appropriately so let's start up the
适当地让我们开始
application again then try and hit the
再次申请，然后尝试点击
the strong hitters thread dump punches
强大的击球手
sometimes sensitive here you see it's
有时在这里你会发现它很敏感
asking me for a username and password
要求我输入用户名和密码
and if I escape that I get an error page
如果我逃脱了，我得到一个错误页面
by default we will generate you a unique
默认情况下，我们将为您生成一个唯一的
password each time stop starts but you
每次停止时都输入密码，但是您
can configure that in the logs I'm
可以在我的日志中进行配置
saying in this case I should be you
说在这种情况下我应该是你
should have a small password somewhere
某处应该有一个小密码
in here here it is so this is the
在这里，这就是
password that is generated for me so if
为我生成的密码，如果
I enter that correctly I get the
我输入正确，我得到
endpoints and you can customize all that
端点，您可以自定义所有这些
and in the standard way that you would
并以标准的方式
with any other spring security app
与任何其他Spring Security应用程序一起
so yes I said we have basic security
是的，我说我们有基本的安全保障
enabled by default and if you want to
默认启用，如果您想
customize any of the the end points the
自定义任何终点
passwords then that's really easy to do
密码，那真的很容易
there's documentation on the github
github上有文档
project page the last thing I want to
项目页面我想做的最后一件事
show you is how we've been working with
告诉你我们一直在合作
these new fat jar files and running
这些新的胖子jar文件正在运行
directly from the main method but you
直接从主要方法，但你
can actually use spring boot in a more
实际上可以在更多情况下使用弹簧靴
classic style if you if you want or need
古典风格，如果您想要或需要
to so I'm going to show you how you can
因此，我将向您展示如何
change this application now and deploy
立即更改此应用程序并部署
it within
它内
Tomcat as you may do at the moment so
您目前可能会这样做的Tomcat
it's pretty straightforward all I need
我需要的一切都非常简单
to do is change the packaging type to
要做的就是将包装类型更改为
wall and then I have to refresh your
墙，然后我必须刷新你的
clips I now need to do just one more
现在我只需要再做一个剪辑
thing and that's to give myself a
事情就是给自己一个
servlet initializer that will start the
Servlet初始化程序将启动
project so I'm just call it in it and we
项目，所以我只是称呼它，我们
actually provide a really convenient
实际上提供了一个真正的方便
starting point that nine times out of
起点是九次
ten will work for you so if you have
十个会为你工作，所以如果你有
spring boot servlet initializer you just
您刚刚启动的Spring Boot Servlet初始化程序
need to override one method to tell it
需要重写一种方法来告诉它
the main configuration class so in this
主要配置类
case I want to point it back in my
情况下，我想指出
example class but then rather than
示例类，但不是
running from the main method I'll start
从我将开始的主要方法开始运行
it through eclipse is embedded Tomcat
它通过eclipse嵌入了Tomcat
server so here you see I've got it
服务器，所以在这里您可以看到我的服务器
deployed already if I start that up now
如果我现在开始就已经部署了
see it takes a little bit longer but
看到它需要更长的时间，但是
there's my there's my spring logo for
有我的，有我的春天的标志
boot and then it starts if I head back
开机，如果我回头就开始
over here and hit refresh you'll see
在这里点击刷新，您将看到
that we get a we get a 404 because we're
我们得到一个404，因为我们
no longer the root project I need to add
不再需要添加根项目
the context root and then it's asking
上下文根，然后问
you for the security again
再次保证您的安全
we just take out security to show you
我们只是拿出安全带给你看
that app still works
该应用仍然有效
okay there we go erm there's the there's
好吧，我们去吧，那里
the app now running deployed in tomcat
现在运行的应用程序已部署在tomcat中
one of the nice things about this is if
与此有关的一件好事是
you actually jump back into the maven
你实际上跳回了行家
build and build it again if you look at
如果您看一下，请再次构建并重新构建它
the target directory you'll see that we
目标目录，您将看到我们
still have two copies of our archive we
仍然有我们存档的两个副本
have the original one which is obviously
有原始的那显然是
bigger than it previously was but we
比以前更大，但我们
still have a rewritten one and this
还有一个改写的
allows us to actually still run this war
允许我们实际上仍然进行这场战争
application as if it was her as if it
申请就好像是她一样
was a command line app so I can still
是一个命令行应用程序，所以我仍然可以
run Java that's jar and then the name of
运行jar的Java，然后运行
the war file if you've ever used
战争档案（如果您曾经使用过）
anything like Jenkins this is a common
像詹金斯这样的东西很常见
way that you can ship an application
您可以发布应用程序的方式
it's really useful because you can have
这真的很有用，因为您可以
people just run it or deploy it into
人们只是运行它或将其部署到
their own application server if that's
他们自己的应用服务器，如果那是
what they prefer to do so hopefully
他们希望这样做的希望
you've enjoyed this brief tour if you
如果您喜欢这个简短的旅游，
want to find out more we have
想了解更多
documentation on the project's page
项目页面上的文档
projects bring to i/o and the github
项目带到I / O和github
project itself is where we're hosting
项目本身就是我们托管的地方
all the code and we're Apache 2 license
所有的代码，我们是Apache 2许可证
and we're looking for any issues that
我们正在寻找任何问题
you've got please raise in there or any
你必须在那里加薪
pull requests that you want to put in
拉出您要放入的请求
we're looking for contributions so
我们正在寻找贡献，所以
please get involved will also be logging
请参与也将记录
a little bit about this as we go on if
关于这一点，我们继续
you look at the new spring website
你看一下新的春季网站
spring the IO you may be interested know
春天你可能感兴趣的IO
that this is actually a spring boot
这实际上是一个弹簧靴
application so we are actually using
应用程序，所以我们实际上正在使用
this ourselves within production this
这个我们在生产中
presentation itself is available on my
演示文稿本身可以在我的
github page and if you want to contact
github页面，如果您想联系
either myself or Dave who is the other
我自己或戴夫是谁
co-lead then I'll contact details are on
然后，我将联系详细信息
the screen there so that I think we've
屏幕在那里，所以我认为我们已经
got time for questions if there are any
有时间提问
oh yes yes quite a bunch I'm gonna get a
哦，是的，有很多我会得到一个
live crowd for you here arm yeah so Dave
活着的人在这里为你服务，所以戴夫
of course has been
当然是
fantastic on just being right on top of
恰好位于顶部
it answering all the questions so he's
它回答了所有问题，所以他是
answered pretty much all of them but I
他们几乎都回答了，但我
think we can go back and pick a couple
认为我们可以回去挑选一对
for folks for the 290 people still on
对于仍在290人的人们
the phone if you have additional
如果您还有其他电话
questions now is a great time to answer
现在的问题是回答的好时机
them
他们
excuse me get to enter them into the Q&amp;A
请原谅我进入问答环节
panel but let's start with a couple
面板，但让我们从几个开始
until and I see any brand new ones top
直到我看到任何全新的顶部
off the plate at the moment on okay so
暂时关闭盘子，这样
good one was um I think I think this is
好人是嗯，我想我认为这是
interesting because it uh it just talks
有趣，因为它只是在说话
about how spring food might work with
关于春季食物可能如何搭配
things outside of the spring ecosystem I
春天生态系统之外的东西我
think it's an important topic of Mubeen
认为这是Mubeen的重要话题
Kahn asks with applications that using
卡恩（Kahn）提出的申请要求
the mixes spring the catchy CSS for rust
混合物使上钩的CSS生锈
services how would spring boot work in
服务spring boot如何工作
that situation and uh Dave responds it
这种情况，而戴夫回应了
would work what we lose some of the
会工作，我们会失去一些
magic um you guys want to talk about
你们想谈谈魔术
writing your own plugin for boot perhaps
编写自己的启动插件
that would support CSS cxf features you
将支持您的CSS cxf功能
talked a little bit about that yeah sure
谈了一点
um so certainly we've tried to design
嗯，当然我们已经尝试设计
spring boots so that you can opt in to
spring boot ，这样您就可以选择加入
as much as you want so you'll notice
随心所欲，您会注意到
that the auto configuration is something
自动配置是什么
you have to opt into so you're free to
您必须选择加入，这样您就可以自由选择
use any kind of existing technologies
使用任何现有技术
you other demos you don't need to
您不需要的其他演示
necessarily use the jar approach you
必须使用jar方法
could you could deploy in a classic Wow
你可以部署在经典的哇吗
and you may need to do a bit of work if
如果您可能需要做一些工作
you're going a little bit off the beaten
你要离开人迹罕至的地方
track for the things that we recommended
跟踪我们推荐的东西
but it's um it's pretty straightforward
嗯，这很简单
to do it's also you may notice that when
您也可能会注意到
I added actuator that the functionality
我添加了执行器功能
was automatically enabled and you can
已自动启用，您可以
distribute auto configuration settings
分发自动配置设置
actually within your own projects if you
实际上在您自己的项目中，如果您
want to so it would be pretty
想要这样会很漂亮
straightforward to write something you
直接写一些你的东西
know to add auto configuration for your
知道为您添加自动配置
particular thing if that's what you need
如果那是您需要的特别的东西
so that's that's another thing that I
所以那是我的另一件事
think a lot of people may be interested
认为很多人可能会感兴趣
in in the future
在未来
excellent um couple couple questions
优秀的恩爱夫妻问题
coming in that Dave's answering in
进入戴夫的回答
real-time here and I think this one is
实时在这里，我认为这是
particularly worth repeating a question
特别值得重复一个问题
as from Devi Kieran he asks so spring
从德维·基兰（Devi Kieran）那里他问到
booth an application server or a web
摊位应用程序服务器或Web
server
服务器
I need Dave or Dave response with
我需要Dave或Dave回应
neither uh but you would you if you
既不是呃，但是如果你
would talk about that for a moment I
我会谈一会儿
think that's a very important question
认为这是一个非常重要的问题
yeah
是的
so spring boot is isn't either but it
所以 spring boot 也不是，但是
does offer first-class support for
确实提供了一流的支持
embedded servlet containers so spring
嵌入式servlet容器在春天
boot is really about starting a spring
开机真的是要开始一个春天
application context that's his main goal
应用程序上下文是他的主要目标
so if you're dealing with a batch
因此，如果您要处理一批
application that obviously means that
显然意味着
you're not dealing with web web content
您不是在处理网页内容
necessarily but once you've got that
一定要，但是一旦你知道了
application context up and running
应用程序上下文启动并运行
another aspect of spring boot kicks in
弹簧靴的另一方面
which gives you first class support for
为您提供一流的支持
embedded Tomcat so in the demos that
嵌入式Tomcat，因此在演示中
I've shown here we've been using
我在这里展示了我们一直在使用
embedded Tomcat and that's that's kicked
嵌入式Tomcat就是这样
in and handled the web request but also
并处理了Web请求，而且
don't forget you can quite happily throw
别忘了你可以很开心地扔
all that away and just deploy you know a
所有这一切，只要部署就可以了
boot application in whatever existing
在现有的环境中启动应用程序
application server you use there's
您使用的应用服务器
nothing particularly magical about the
没有什么特别神奇的
that main method you can you can pick
你可以选择的主要方法
and choose the bits of spring things
然后选择春天的东西
that you want awesome and I follow on
你想要很棒，我继续
question that's definitely related from
肯定与之相关的问题
Judy Bruce why would you invent Tomcat
朱迪·布鲁斯（Judy Bruce）为什么要发明Tomcat
why would you embed Tomcat was that the
你为什么要嵌入Tomcat是
question
题
that day exactly correct yes right okay
那天完全正确是是好的
well it you know again it depends on the
好吧，你再次知道这取决于
style of application you're writing a
您正在编写的应用程序样式
lot of the spring bead functionality was
弹簧珠的功能很多
actually driven by customer requests so
实际上是受客户要求驱动的
we're finding a lot of a lot of teams
我们发现了很多团队
are working in a much more kind of
正在以更多的方式工作
DevOps e-way building self-contained
DevOps e-way建筑物自成体系
apps and then throwing them across the
应用，然后将它们扔到
wire there's a lot less to configure if
电线要配置的东西要少得多
you're in control of it obviously you
你很容易控制它
know when you run with Java - JAL are
知道何时使用Java运行-JAL是
the same thing runs
同一件事
as long as you got the same version of
只要您拥有相同版本的
Java the same thing runs wherever you
Java无论您在何处都可以运行
are which is really helpful you don't
真的对您没有帮助
have to configure an application server
必须配置一个应用服务器
or set it up we're also finding it works
或进行设置，我们也发现它可行
really really well with cloud-based
基于云的技术真的很好
deployments so Cloud Foundry is a
部署，因此Cloud Foundry是
classic example where the spring the i/o
春天的I / O的经典例子
website is running on Cloud Foundry and
网站正在Cloud Foundry上运行，并且
just embedding Tomcat means there is a
嵌入Tomcat意味着有一个
lot less to worry about because you're
不用担心，因为你
you know you're in control of everything
你知道你掌控一切
that app is just something that that
该应用只是
runs on that cloud environment you don't
在您没有的云环境上运行
have to worry about the way that that
不得不担心那种方式
cloud environment may have configured
云环境可能已配置
their application server yeah excellent
他们的应用服务器不错
they saw another very important question
他们看到了另一个非常重要的问题
from Eric Nils do you have a rough
来自埃里克·尼尔斯（Eric Nils）
estimate on when this will become GA or
估计何时将成为GA或
want to have an initial one data release
想要发布一个初始数据
yeah we we are actually building on
是的，我们实际上是在
spring for functionality so we won't be
功能的春天，所以我们不会
able to release the GA until spring 4 is
能够释放GA，直到弹簧4
released and that should be happening
被释放，那应该正在发生
before the end of the year so we're
在今年年底之前，所以我们
probably looking at a spring boot
可能正在看 spring boot
release around the end of the year or
大约在年底发布或
possibly early next year it is we're
可能是明年年初，这是我们
saying we have milestones that are out
说我们有一些里程碑
there now and we're fairly confident in
现在在那里，我们对
them especially as we're running our own
他们尤其是在我们自己运行时
site with with them so you know you can
与他们一起工作，以便您可以
certainly give it a go down you have got
当然可以给它一个机会
stability in terms of the most own
最稳定的方面
releases even if you know you don't want
释放，即使您知道自己不想要
to run on the snapshots you can you can
在快照上运行，您可以
consider the milestones yeah we're
考虑里程碑，是的
running in a Java one at the booth
在展位上以Java语言运行
worked great though and for folks that
虽然效果很好，但对于人们来说
may be unaware Spring Framework 4 o on
可能不知道Spring Framework 4或更高版本
which spring booth depends weird you
哪个春季展台取决于您
know typical are typical release canes
知道典型的是典型的释放手杖
for that is at the very end of the year
因为那是在今年年底
or the or the very beginning of 2014 so
或2014年初
you know you'll be you'll be stating
你知道你会的，你会说
spring boot and spring framework in that
Spring Boot和Spring框架在那
timeframe ok let's see
好的时间，让我们看看
Eric Mills asks another good question do
埃里克·米尔斯（Eric Mills）问另一个好问题吗
you expect any more major API changes
您期望API有更多重大更改
before GA or is this safe
在GA之前还是这样安全
start using in new production
开始在新产品中使用
applications today so I guess we're not
今天的应用程序，所以我想我们不是
really expecting any major API changes
真的期待任何重大的API更改
on the things that you would like to use
在您想使用的东西上
yourself directly so for instance that
直接自己，例如
spring application class is it's been
春天的应用程序类
fairly stable now for a while I guess
我猜现在已经相当稳定了
some of the internals may change so if
一些内部可能会改变，所以如果
you're writing your own auto
你正在写自己的汽车
configuration classes you know I guess
你知道我猜的配置类
we reserve the right to change that but
我们保留对此进行更改的权利，但
if you're actually just using it as a
如果您实际上只是将其用作
consumer you should be fairly well
消费者你应该还不错
insulated and I think it's relatively
绝缘的，我认为这是相对的
safe to use we certainly won't be making
使用安全，我们当然不会
any major changes like a salient spring
任何重大变化，例如明显的春天
site itself is running on it and I don't
网站本身正在运行，但我没有
think they'll be too happy if we broke
认为如果我们破产了他们会太高兴
everything absolutely
一切都绝对
yeah Dave Dave Dave's answer greeted
是的，Dave Dave Dave的回答表示欢迎
agrees with you but he also you know
同意你，但他也知道
makes the know hey you know no no
让你知道，嘿，你知道，不，不，
absolute guarantees here at disclaimer
绝对免责声明
so but it sounds
所以听起来
Eric sounds uh unlikely so I think you
埃里克（Eric）听起来不太可能，所以我想你
you know need to make a judgment call
你知道需要打个电话
there for yourself figure out yes I mean
自己找出是的，我的意思是
the more in the guts of the project you
项目的胆量越多，您
you're taking you know the more likely
你带你知道更有可能
it is that we we may want to change
是我们可能要改变
something but I think as you noticed the
某些东西，但我认为正如您所注意到的
app that I wrote really didn't call that
我写的应用真的没有
much of spring boots itself so you
spring boot 本身很多，所以你
should be fairly safe okay yeah and and
应该是相当安全的，是的，并且
Eric thanks for that question I mean
埃里克（Eric）感谢我的意思
were that's such a nice compliment to
那是对...的很好的赞美吗
hear after you know just getting
知道之后就听到
introduced to technology you know you're
介绍了您知道的技术
you're excited to use it already that's
您已经很高兴使用它了
that's that's just fantastic so um
那真是太棒了
thanks for that and uh let's see um Wow
谢谢你，让我们来看看哇
geez questions just keep coming in this
哎呀问题一直在这
is uh Dave Dave tires just machine here
是Dave Dave的轮胎吗？
um so let's see a Greg Proctor asks if
嗯，让我们来看看Greg Proctor问
we have some sort of a diagram that
我们有某种图表，
shows boot and its relationship to other
显示启动及其与其他的关系
components and I was going to draw his
组件，我要画他的
attention to the keynote slides on
注意幻灯片上的主题
unknowns from 1 to 2 X book and I just
从1到2本书的未知数，我只是
realized that not everyone has those yet
意识到不是每个人都拥有这些
so um
嗯
be posting the day 1 keynote from spring
从春季发布第一天主题演讲
one where there is exactly such a
一个完全有这样的地方
diagram um but in the meantime filth
图um但与此同时污秽
memory serves you had something kind of
记忆为您服务
some sort of basic diagram on the on the
上的某种基本图
from the blog where you introduced the
从您介绍的博客
yeah I think there's probably something
是的，我认为可能是有些东西
in the spring warm presentation that we
在春季温暖的演讲中，我们
gave as well which you can probably find
以及你可能会发现的
on Dave's github account dead beasts are
在戴夫的github帐户上，死兽是
calm slash presence I think and that
我认为那是平静的斜线存在
will provide you a breakdown of the
将为您提供细分
spring boot modules that we use
我们使用的spring boot模块
internally in terms of the kind of the
在内部就种类而言
bigger picture of what spring pod
什么弹簧吊舱的大图
projects are available then I think the
项目可用，然后我认为
the day one keynote will be really
第一天的主题演讲将是
useful when that's published and also if
在发布时以及在
you if you jump on over to the github
你，如果你跳到github
project spring boot there are a whole
项目春季启动有一个整体
bunch of sample applications you can
一堆示例应用程序，您可以
look at which show you the kind of basic
看哪个显示你的基本
basic spring projects that we've got
我们拥有的基本春季项目
coverage for at the moment guys I guess
我猜目前的报道
I guess just one more thing I guess the
我猜只是一件事
the getting started guides on the new
新产品入门指南
spring i/o website are also really good
春天的I / O网站也真的很好
overview of the complete spring
整个弹簧的概述
ecosystem excellent thank you all right
生态系统非常好，谢谢
boy it's just just coming in on let's
男孩，只是来吧，让我们
yeah it's a question later
是的，稍后再问
excuse my question a little bit earlier
请问我的问题早一点
that Dave answered that I thought I
戴夫回答我以为我
thought would be good um and it was you
以为会很好，那是你
know sort of what type of spring
知道什么样的弹簧
projects should we use boot for should
我们应该使用boot进行的项目
we not use food for when should you use
我们不应该在什么时候使用食物
spring boot and uh David thought I had a
spring boot ，呃大卫以为我有一个
really interesting answer which was just
真的很有趣的答案
hey wherever you use spring but I just
嘿，无论您在哪里使用弹簧，但我只是
thought maybe you could talk about that
以为也许你可以谈谈
a little bit so yeah I completely agree
一点点，是的，我完全同意
with Dave's arm especially it's um I
戴夫的手臂，尤其是我
mean yeah we're hopefully not giving you
是的，是的，我们希望不给你
a huge footprint in spring boot and just
spring boot 的巨大足迹
trying to introduce
试图介绍
to spring as a whole so certainly I
整个春天，所以我肯定
don't think there's many areas where it
不要以为有很多地方
would hurt to use spring boot and I can
使用弹簧靴会很痛，我可以
say you have so many deployment options
说你有这么多的部署选项
you know you can use this embedded jar
你知道你可以使用这个嵌入式罐子
or you can deploy in a classic sense so
或者您可以按照经典的方式进行部署
I can't think of many places where I
我想不起很多地方
wouldn't consider it
不会考虑
I guess it's at some point if you're if
我想这是某个时候
you are writing your own application and
您正在编写自己的应用程序，
you end up with completely your own
你最终完全是自己的
configuration and you're deploying to
配置，然后部署到
awhile far you may wonder you know is
一会儿你可能会想知道
that is there the point to it of that at
那就是它的意义所在
that stage but certainly most apps I
那个阶段，但是我可以肯定大多数应用
think will benefit from it actually
认为实际上会从中受益
excellent ok um see you again at the
很好，很好，下次再见
time oh I should just mention a couple
时间哦，我只想提几个
people have asked if there's a tutorial
人们问是否有教程
or a presentation online somewhere and
或某处在线演示，
certainly you should check out the
当然，您应该检查一下
initial blog entry where Phil and Dan
Phil和Dan的最初博客条目
introduced spring boots so I'll I'll
介绍了 spring boot ，所以我会
post that into the Q&amp;A window but I
将其发布到“问答”窗口中，但我
think it's also important to note that a
认为注意以下几点也很重要
lot of the new guides that we have
我们有很多新指南
introduced on spring do also are using
在春天介绍的确也正在使用
spring boots and there's there's just a
spring boot ，那里只有一个
whole ton of new content in terms of
整吨的新内容
guides and tutorials so I just want to
指南和教程，所以我只想
encourage people to check out those
鼓励人们检查那些
resources as well let's see so this may
资源，让我们看看，所以这可能
be fairly straightforward but I thought
相当简单，但我认为
it might be worth mentioning Benjamin
也许值得一提的是本杰明
nitin asks you know are these jars
尼丁问你知道这些罐子吗
executable and Dave responded with you
可执行文件，戴夫与您回应
know a jar created with the spring
知道春天创造的罐子
bhutanese executable and you can also
不丹可执行文件，您还可以
use something like the maven shade
使用类似Maven的阴影
plugin is there any more you want to say
插件还有更多您想说的吗
about that or is that just kind of
关于还是那个
straightforward open shot well it's an
简单明了的开枪
interesting subject upon putting more
放置更多有趣的主题
than we've got time for Java itself
比我们有时间去做Java本身
doesn't really offer first
并不真正提供第一
support for for these kind of shaded or
支持这些阴影或
fat jars so that you always have to jump
胖罐子，所以你总是要跳
through some hoops and we think that the
通过一些箍，我们认为
the solution that we've got is is one of
我们得到的解决方案是其中之一
the better ones it does present you know
它呈现的更好的东西，你知道
like a nice easy view of your
就像一个很好的简单视图
dependencies not everything's unpacked
依赖不是所有东西都被解压了
and repacked which is nice but you may
并重新包装，这很好，但你可能
still hit problems with it especially if
仍然遇到问题，特别是如果
you've got third-party libraries that
您有第三方库
are doing class path scanning you have
正在进行类路径扫描
to be um they have to be doing it in a
是的，他们必须在一个
certain way to make sure that it doesn't
确保它不会的某种方法
go wrong so here you have different
出问题了，所以这里你有不同
options there and if it doesn't work if
选项在那里，如果它不起作用，如果
you jump out but in practice we've found
你跳出来，但实际上我们发现
that most things have worked for us and
大多数事情对我们都起作用，
if you do find something that fails
如果您发现失败的地方
please raise an issue because we've been
请提出一个问题，因为我们一直
able to find workarounds for some you
能够为您找到一些解决方法
know dependencies that we've had
知道我们已经有了依赖
problems with ourselves and so so it may
我们自己的问题等等
be possible that we can can get things
有可能我们可以得到东西
working for you if you do find something
如果您找到了东西，就会为您工作
doesn't work in that style yep um oh and
不适合这种风格哦，哦，
there was another question the stack I
我还有另一个问题
wanted to highlight because I think it
想突出显示，因为我认为
speaks you people who work at it you
会告诉你努力工作的人
know I see shops that are kind of doing
知道我看到商店正在做
this a little more traditional style so
这有点传统风格
channel 3 asks hey if I want to update
频道3问我是否要更新
whether it's a web that XML how do I do
不管是XML的网站，我该怎么办
that and uh
那和呃
Davers saw a david response you know we
戴佛斯看到了大卫的回应，你知道我们
recommend not using works in web.xml but
建议不要在web.xml中使用作品，但
if you need to for some reason you just
如果您出于某些原因需要，
you have to edit your own source code
您必须编辑自己的源代码
because you send a little bit more about
因为您发送了更多有关
that and just you know speak to the
那，而你知道跟
people that are kind of you know having
你们那种人都知道
to a force to work or have to work with
工作或必须与之合作的力量
sort of more traditional java ee set up
较传统的Java ee设置
yeah sure um so I guess we provide these
是的，嗯，我想我们提供这些
convenience methods but they they do
方便的方法，但他们确实
kind of assume that you're in a servant
有点假设你在仆人中
3 environment so you can have a servlet
3个环境，因此您可以拥有一个servlet
initializer if you can't remember that
初始化器，如果您不记得了
and you need to use a web XML there's no
而且您需要使用网络XML
reason why you can't start up a classic
为什么你不能开始经典
spring application context and use that
弹簧应用程序上下文并使用
enable auto configuration annotation on
在启用自动配置注释
a regular app configuration spring class
常规的应用程序配置春季课程
so that's another way of kind of hook
这是另一种挂钩方式
yourself into it what we don't really
自己投入其中，我们并不是真的
recommend or support at the moment is
目前推荐或支持的是
having been XML as this entry point you
一直以XML作为此入口点
can still have being XML but you really
仍然可以是XML，但实际上
want a configuration class as your
想要一个配置类作为您的
starting point and then import being XML
起点，然后导入为XML
if that's what you need to run we don't
如果那是您需要运行的，我们不需要
recommend that you start with XML
建议您从XML开始
excellent ok let's see a couple of
好的，让我们看看几个
others coming in on a question from
其他人来自一个问题
Santa isn't the actuators studio
圣诞老人不是执行器工作室
addressing mechanism to monitor and
监控和寻址机制
debug the non-functional stuff why would
调试无功能的东西为什么会
the decision made to add and package
决定添加和打包
them with CF why was the decision made
他们与CF为什么决定
to atom practice them with the with the
原子与一起练习
app in the demo or as a general source
演示中或作为一般来源的应用程序
why they send us a package I think it's
他们为什么向我们发送包裹，我认为是
a general arm but Santa if you were
一般的手臂，但圣诞老人，如果你是
still on the phone please feel free to
仍在电话中，请随时
clarify but that's kind of what I'm
澄清一下，但这就是我的意思
inferring from from the question okay I
从问题中推断出
mean I guess the main reason is because
意思是我想主要原因是
once once you've got this thing level of
一旦你有了这个东西的水平
an in production it kind of makes sense
在生产中这很有意义
to have those features always available
使这些功能始终可用
I know that the guys that the website
我知道那个网站
found the actuator stuff really really
发现执行器的东西真的很
useful just in terms of debugging you
仅对调试您有用
know a particular request went wrong
知道一个特定的请求出了错
what was those last requests you know
您最近知道的那些请求是什么
they also with the with the new website
他们还与新网站一起
they run a dual deployments so they've
他们运行双重部署，因此他们已经
always got continuous uptime and just
总是有连续的正常运行时间
little things like getting the info
小事情，例如获取信息
endpoint to tell you which particular
端点告诉您哪个特定
build is running in the live environment
构建在实时环境中运行
is really useful so I guess the question
真的很有用，所以我想这个问题
is why wouldn't you want them in the it
这就是为什么你不想要他们
deployed with your app yes a cyntha does
与您的应用程序一起部署cyntha可以
go on to clarify on he or she just
继续澄清他或她
responded he or she spotted a moment ago
回答他或她刚才发现
so you just in general why would I make
所以你总的来说我为什么要
them part of the app and I think you I
他们的应用程序的一部分，我想你我
think you addressed that okay um
认为你说的好吧
excellent okay um let's see well I think
很好，嗯，我想看看
you cover this there was someone asking
你盖这个，有人问
about embedded data source options but I
关于嵌入式数据源选项，但我
think you covered the h2 or hsqldb
认为您涵盖了h2或hsqldb
by a staff of the dermal yeah those are
由皮肤是的人员是
those are supported outer box as in as
那些被支持的外盒如
is Darby and obviously if if you need
是达比，很明显，如果您需要
something else you know that you think
你知道的其他东西
we should all take a figure then sends
我们都应该拿一个数字然后发送
an issue but you'll feel free to use the
一个问题，但您可以随时使用
standard embedded database the board
标准嵌入式数据库板
that's with spring and we just won't get
那是春天，我们就不会
involved then so you can you can wire up
然后参与其中，以便您可以进行连线
anything you would with normal spring as
您在正常春季时所做的一切
well gotcha gotcha
好吧，你好
um you know there's a couple people
嗯，你知道有几个人
commenting you know the one person
评论你认识一个人
comments this is a question per se but a
评论这本身就是一个问题，但是
comment and then just I'll form a
发表评论，然后我将形成一个
question under this in just a moment
片刻之下在此问题
Phil so a couple of people saying hey
菲尔，所以几个人都说嘿
this looks similar to me to what I've
这看起来和我类似
seen in blank right and you know I love
看到空白右边，你知道我爱
it it's awesome um wouldn't you find
它很棒，你不会找到
some of the inspirations for spring boot
spring boot 的一些灵感
have been and you know in that in those
曾经，你知道在那些
initial customer conversations where we
最初的客户对话，我们
were you know having having them having
你知道有他们有
the discussion right you know what were
讨论的权利，你知道是什么
some other inspirations that that that
其他一些灵感
helped you know bring spring food to
帮助您知道将春季食品带到
life you sure or something yeah yeah we
生活肯定吗，是的，我们
actually looked at a number of different
实际上看了一些不同的
projects both within the kind of Java
项目都在Java之内
world and and outside of it so certainly
世界及其外部
crop wizard has been mentioned in number
提到了裁剪向导
of times and that was certainly a very
的时间，那当然是非常
big influence and a lot of people were
巨大的影响力和很多人
saying how much they enjoy working with
说他们喜欢与他人一起工作
that stylus deployments and so that was
手写笔的部署，所以
one half pipe was another that we looked
一个半管是我们看过的另一个
into as well as you know things in the
以及你所知道的
Ruby world like Sinatra that a you know
像Sinatra这样的Ruby世界
very popular awesome thanks for that
非常受欢迎的感谢
okay so this isn't interesting this is
好吧，这没意思，这是
an interesting one I think I think we're
我认为我认为我们很有趣
almost almost out of time here but uh
在这里几乎快没时间了，但是
okay I think there's two more questions
好吧，我认为还有两个问题
coming in and I think if you don't mind
进来，我想如果你不介意
we'll go a little bit over exertional
我们会花点力气
yeah no problem
是的没问题
yeah okay cool all right thanks I'm sure
是的，很好，很酷，谢谢，我确定
there folks on the phone will appreciate
电话里的人们会很感激
it because um we still do have gosh 194
这是因为嗯，我们仍然有天哪194
people on the phones awesome on
电话上的人真棒
so yeah keep your questions coming folks
所以是的，让您的问题不断出现
um so let's see uh two questions on do
嗯，让我们来看看呃两个问题
you integrate with spring data and
您与spring数据集成
regular grade Proctor asks yes we do
普通成绩Proctor要求我们这样做
yeah if you have a look at me sample
是的，如果你看看我的样品
applications but actually it's it's
应用程序，但实际上是
pretty straightforward let me see if I
很简单，让我看看我是否
can find it can you still see my screen
可以找到它，你还能看到我的屏幕吗
yes yeah you're coming into this phone
是的，是的，您正在使用此手机
fill so in in the spring booth github
填写春季展位github
repo there is a bunch of samples and if
回购有很多样品，如果
you take a look at the spring sample
你看一下春季样品
data JP a there's a there's a really
数据JP有一个真的
simple kind of example that uses the
使用以下示例的简单示例
spring data repositories if I can ever
如果可以的话， spring data 存储库
get through the package structure effect
通过包装结构效果
yeah so they're there for instance is an
是的，所以他们在那里，例如
example of a spring data repository that
春天数据存储库的示例
will get picked up automatically so
会自动捡起，所以
that's probably the best place to have a
那可能是拥有一个最好的地方
look that's a github spring - projects
看起来是github的春天-项目
spring - but-- and then under the spring
春天-但是-然后在春天下
view samples you'll find you'll find it
查看样品，您会找到的
and I gave makes a good point in
我给了一个很好的观点
answering in the chat that you know we
在聊天中回答您知道我们的情况
do have a number of external community
确实有一些外部社区
presenters excuse me community commuters
主持人请问社区通勤者
that contribute coded spring data and
贡献编码的弹簧数据并
you know we're certainly looking for
你知道我们肯定在找
contributors and new committers way as
贡献者和新提交者的方式
we as we mentioned we support kPa and
正如我们提到的，我们支持kPa和
MongoDB so far and you know there's lots
到目前为止，MongoDB您知道很多
of other no SQL databases out there
其他没有SQL数据库的数据库
right and certainly even just ones we
对的，当然甚至只是我们
support directly with string data so
直接支持字符串数据，因此
would love to you know gracefully
希望您能优雅地认识
receiving contributions and if you're
收到捐款，如果您
curious about how to get involved on you
对如何参与到您感到好奇
know just ping us on a spring central
知道只是在春季中央对我们
it's Twitter and will will will let you
这是Twitter，它将让您
know on check out breaks Rob post as
知道在签出休息罗布发布为
well it's really good for he contributed
对他的贡献真的很好
recently JMS support
最近的JMS支持
documented the whole process which is
记录了整个过程
meeting with well-read that's right
与正确阅读的会面
that's right that was just posted so on
没错，就是刚刚发布的
the spring bio blog yeah there is that
春季生物博客，是的，
great post on aa and he was had a four
在aa上的精彩帖子，他有四个
can contribute right it's just green but
可以做出贡献，这只是绿色，但
yeah yeah so um please have a look at
是的，所以嗯，请看一看
that I'll um I'll post a link I'm here
我会，我会发布一个链接，我在这里
in the chat if I can if I can take it
如果可以的话，在聊天中
out while we're talking here um so
我们在这里聊天的时候
another good question Edwin Cruz asks
埃德温·克鲁兹（Edwin Cruz）提出的另一个好问题
what's the minimum disk and memory
最小磁盘和内存是多少
footprint for fringe spring food I think
我认为春季春季食品的足迹
it's just kind of guessed you you know
只是猜到你知道
hey what's what's the overhead you know
嘿，你知道什么是开销
that I mean that I'm incurring here what
我的意思是我在这里招致什么
price and I pay yeah interesting
价格，我付出是有趣的
actually I've never I've never measured
其实我从来没有测量过
it it's it's an interesting question
这是一个有趣的问题
because it it really depends on what
因为它真的取决于什么
you're using spring food itself is
您正在使用春季食品本身是
fairly light you know there's not a
相当轻，你知道没有
great deal of code in it you know itself
您可以了解其中的大量代码
and it has a lot of optional
它有很多可选的
dependencies that so you know it depends
你知道它依赖的依赖
on what you end up pulling in so you saw
关于你最终拉进来的东西，所以你看到了
that rest example was coming in at about
剩下的例子大约在
10 Meg and I think I've done a spring
10梅格，我想我做了一个春天
data sample that I think rolls in is
我认为要输入的数据样本是
about maybe twelve make you know with
大概十二点让你知道
hibernate and JPA support but you know
休眠和JPA支持，但您知道
it depends on what dependencies you pull
这取决于你拉什么依赖
in as to how big that project gets but
关于那个项目有多大，但是
spring foods itself is pretty light and
春季食品本身很清淡，
I'm going to post that um we're going to
我要发布那个，我们要
post that link I did find that to
发布该链接，我确实找到了
contributing to spring boots so I'm just
为 spring boot 做贡献，所以我只是
going to post that right now to everyone
现在将其发布给所有人
back in response to Greg Proctor's
回应Greg Proctor的
question so working on that right now
问题，所以现在就解决这个问题
okay great on let's see so does Colin
好吧，让我们看看科林
plank asks to spring boot play nicely
木板要求弹簧靴很好玩
with dependent projects that have Spring
具有Spring的相关项目
3.2 transitive dependencies Dave
3.2传递依赖Dave
responds that spring bars required the
回应说弹簧杆需要
Auto config features but that you can
自动配置功能，但您可以
use some of the spring application
使用一些Spring应用程序
features embedded and embedded servers
具有嵌入式和嵌入式服务器的功能
with spring 3 - do you want to say more
春季3-您想说更多吗
about that or with yeah um I guess I
关于这个或者是的，我想我
guess
猜测
the only thing I'd add is that we do
我唯一要补充的是，我们
strive really hard within spring the
在春季内努力奋斗
core framework to retain binary back
保留二进制返回的核心框架
compatibility so if you're not using
兼容性，所以如果您不使用
deprecated features from from three to
不推荐使用的功能从三个
you know if a spring application that's
你知道一个Spring应用程序是否
build against three two doesn't work
针对三个两个进行构建不起作用
with spring for then that's normally
用弹簧，那通常是
considered the bug and you should report
考虑到该错误，您应该报告
it and we will do our best to fix it so
它，我们将尽力解决它，以便
so yeah you need spring for to you
所以是的，你需要春天给你
spring boot but there's no reason why
spring boot ，但没有理由
projects build against older versions of
专案会针对较旧版本的
spring shouldn't be compatible with
春天不应该与
spring fall okay great on so we're down
春天秋天还好，所以我们下来了
you know we're done down from our
你知道我们已经被淘汰了
hardware work we're down to about 150
硬件工作量降至150
people stone the phone so on seems like
人们给电话打了个电话，好像
the the QA is kind of winding up here on
质量检查就此结束了
we're going to just give a couple more
我们要多给一些
couple more moments for folks to ask
还有更多时间让人们问
last questions on while I while you're
当你在我身边时，最后一个问题
thinking about here any last questions
在这里思考任何最后的问题
and if you have any I just want you to
如果有的话，我只想你
realize that we do post replays of the
意识到我们确实发布了
webinars on our YouTube channel which I
我的YouTube频道上的网络研讨会
just posted in the chat window
刚刚发布在聊天窗口中
youtube.com forward slash spring source
youtube.com正斜杠Spring源
dev and we typically take it within you
开发人员，我们通常会将其包含在您的内部
know we say within two weeks but you
知道我们会在两周内说，但是你
know what if things aren't insane around
知道周围事情不是疯了怎么办
here we usually try to get to them
在这里，我们通常尝试去找他们
pretty quickly so so you can look for
很快，所以您可以寻找
the replay on that and then what we try
重播，然后我们尝试
to do is also if there are links to
如果还有链接到
various github repos or sample code
各种github仓库或示例代码
you know presentation slides you know we
你知道演示幻灯片，你知道我们
try to put those in the description of
试着把那些放在
said YouTube video as well so that you
还说YouTube视频，以便您
have something really self-contained
有一些真正独立的东西
you can share with your employees or
您可以与您的员工分享，或者
excuse me your your co-workers you know
对不起，你认识的同事
at a brown-bag lunch or you know at the
在一个棕色袋子的午餐中，或者在
next monthly Tech Talk kind of things so
下个月的Tech Talk这样的事情
oh so I also wanted to destroy your
哦，所以我也想摧毁你的
attention to couple of upcoming webinars
注意即将举行的几场网络研讨会
that are really really interesting and
真的很有趣，
if you are looking and interested in
如果您正在寻找并感兴趣
things like WebSockets
WebSockets之类的东西
or if you're interested in do
或者如果您有兴趣
I've got some pretty cool webinars
我有一些非常酷的网络研讨会
coming up next one is on October October
接下来的一个是十月
3rd which is a Thursday and that's going
第三天是星期四
to be about building big data
关于建立大数据
applications with Hadoop and spring and
Hadoop和spring的应用程序以及
we'll talk quite a bit about the new
我们会谈论很多新的
spring XD project which was the promoted
春季XD项目已被推广
sort of unveiled you know an enlarged
揭开面纱，你知道放大
scale for the first time in that spring
在那个春天第一次缩放
one although we've been having milestone
一个，尽管我们一直具有里程碑
releases throughout throughout 2013 and
在整个2013年和
also we're join us for another webinar
我们也要参加另一个网络研讨会
in October on October 8th and rawson
在10月10日和Rawson
story on chef is going to be talking
关于厨师的故事要讲
about building WebSocket browser apps
关于构建WebSocket浏览器应用程序
with Springs so he'll talk quite a bit
和斯普林斯在一起，所以他会讲很多话
about sort of messaging and working with
关于某种消息传递和使用
sock j/s which is a JavaScript library
sock j / s是一个JavaScript库
that pivotal is instrumental in
关键在
contributing to so he'll be doing that
做出贡献，所以他会这样做
on Tuesday October 8th at 3 p.m. and if
10月8日星期二下午3点，如果
you're interested to register just go to
您有兴趣报名只是去
the spring dot IO website and look at
spring dot IO网站，看看
the blog and if you look in the news you
博客，如果您查看新闻，
didn't leave the all posts feed or just
没有留下所有帖子提要或只是
the news and events feed you'll see the
新闻和事件供稿，您将看到
you'll see posts - - and links to those
您会看到帖子--以及这些链接
two webinars so by the way I had one
两个网络研讨会，所以我有一个
request just while we're finishing up
刚完成时要求
here Phil could you bring back that
菲尔，你能把那带回来吗
slide that has kind of the main URL
具有主要网址的幻灯片
links thank you yeah I felt like and
链接谢谢，是的，我觉得
thank you for mentioning that
谢谢你提到
Manji yeah I usually try to remember to
是的，我通常会记得
do that while we're doing the QA but ok
在执行质量检查时执行此操作，但可以
wonderful yes so on you can see the
太好了，所以您可以看到
documentation links right there and you
文档链接就在那里，您也可以
get on page link right there and again
获得页面链接一次又一次
there's a blog entry or two in the blog
博客中有一个或两个博客条目
feed currently on the string that I oh
目前正在喂我哦
that I think what will interest you in a
我认为您会感兴趣的是
related to string boots on Dave and Phil
与戴夫和菲尔的弦靴有关
are very approachable and findable on
是很平易近人的
Twitter or or email so um but just want
Twitter或电子邮件如此，但只想
to share Phil and Dave a lot
分享菲尔和戴夫
comments of wow this is you know thank
哇的评论，这是你知道的谢谢
you so much of the answers and this
你这么多的答案，这
thing is awesome and you know just some
事情很棒，你知道一些
some really cool comments in the chat
聊天中一些非常酷的评论
here so you know it's no wonder that you
在这里，所以您知道这也就不足为奇了
guys were the runaway favorite
那些人是失控的最爱
presentation at Spring one this year and
在今年春季的演讲，以及
you know congratulations this is just
你知道恭喜，这只是
some really cool stuff so thanks for
一些非常酷的东西，所以谢谢
your time guys and you want to say
你的时间家伙，你想说
anything in closing now is a great fun
现在一切都很好玩
just thanks everyone for watching and
只是感谢大家的收看和
looking forward to any feedback you
期待您的任何反馈
might have Cheers take everyone hope
可能让欢呼声带给大家希望
sees the next webinars have a great
看到下届网络研讨会非常精彩
thing
事情